easy-forex.com 2014-05-25

# Privacy Policy | easy-forex

Please wait...

By registering with or accessing the easy forex website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal data.

## Personal Data

The personal data that we collect from you is safely stored via physical, electronic means and procedural controls, in accordance with applicable legislation and it is treated CONFIDENTIAL, at all times.

These controls are reasonably designed to: (i) ensure the security and confidentiality of the customer’s records and information; (ii) protect against any threats or hazards to the security or integrity of the customer’s records and information; and (iii) protect against unauthorized access to or use of customer’s records or information that could result in substantial harm or inconvenience to the customer.

## What kind of information we collect from you?

Throughout our cooperation we may collect information directly from you. Such information may be Personal Data such as your name, DOB, email, address, bank details, financial situation, trading activity, transaction history account balance information, and certain “KYC” documentation. 

We may also collect indirect information from you, which we use purely for verification and security purposes. Such information may include your (IP) address, browser type, operating system, Internet service provider (ISP), MAC id, cookies.

## Data Management

Your security and data protection is our ultimate goal. easy forex does not distribute, sell or transfer any data of its Clients to any unauthorized, non-affiliated to it, third parties. easy forex may disclose data to third parties, always on a “need to know” basis, for the provision of specific services to easy forex and its customers.

easy forex may enter into cooperation agreements with non-affiliated third parties to improve the customer services and to carry out functions, such as client services, consumer behavior surveys or similar activities relevant to business.

## Marketing and Communication

easy forex may contact you by electronic or other form of communication, at any time to provide you with information on its products, marketing materials, training or to enquire evaluation of its services. You may opt out from this application at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link situated at the end each email sent to you or by notifying the member of staff that contacted you.
